ANGEL CAMARGO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER



adcamargo10@gmail.com



https://acamargoportfolio.netlify.app/



B2 - ENGLISH LEVEL



https://www.linkedin.com/in/angel-camargo-942127241/



https://github.com/AngelCamargo4O4

ABOUT ME

Graduated as a informatic engineer at Universidad Rafael Belloso Chacin, having more than 6 years learning, and almost 3 years of demonstrable experience creating web apps, coding mainly in modern JavaScript, React Native, React.js, Node.js, SQL/NOSQL DBs, PHP +7.O/+8.O, Laravel, Tailwindcss, Bootstrap, HTML and CSS, constantly learning. Good teamworker with an impeccable reputation as a programmer, experience working remotely.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSIDAD RAFAEL BELLOSO CHACIN

Informatic Engineering, Aug 2018 - Nov 2022

UDEMY

HTML, CSS JS PHP and Laravel Developer - MernStack Developer, and others. 2021 - 2023

EXPERIENCE

BLUECARIBU - COLOMBIA (CONTRACT/REMOTE) FullStack Web Developer creating multiple web projects

March 2023 - Jan 2024

bluecaribu !*

- I created an app from scratch using JavaScript (react, node, socket.io, mongodb, and more).
- I have created some new features and updated other functionalities previously built.
- I fixed some bugs debugging functions of the app.
- Fast learner and problem solver.

ALFA CO SAC - PERU (FREELANCE/REMOTE) FullStack Web Developer creating JavaScript/PHP app and other features Jul 2022 - Sep 2023 (Alfa Co

- I made an API REST to make the connection between a mobile app and the database, using JavaScript/PHP.
- I created an administrative app from zero satisfying client needs using JavaScript/PHP.
- · Making new features and fixing bugs.
- I created the entire database from scratch using MySQL and connecting db and client with PHP and JavaScript.

SOUSTITREUR - CANADA (FREELANCE/REMOTE) FullStack Web Developer - creating fixing and

updating functionalities of main and other projects

Aug 2023 - Jun 2024





- Migrating current functions of main project to secondary project and mobile app.
- Fixing bugs, sometimes finding them without any information about it.
- Updating functionalities and creating new important features they need for soustitreur and pluscrew project.

SKILLS

Advanced: JS - PHP - React.js - Node.js - NOSQL - SQL -

Relational/No relational DBs - MongoDB - MySQL

Intermediate: Next.js - Express.js - Vue.js - React Native -

Laravel 9 - Heroku - HTML5 & CSS3

Moderate: AWS - Codeigniter 4 - Python - Socket.io

Soft Skills: Teamworker - Self-taught - Fast Learner